const mondai = [
    { number: 1, question: '8631 − 3769 =', answer: '4862', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 2, question: '8604 − 2916 =', answer: '5688', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 3, question: '5200 − 1684 =', answer: '3516', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 4, question: '7413 − 1857 =', answer: '5556', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 5, question: '5863 − 2996 =', answer: '2867', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 6, question: '7642 − 3858 =', answer: '3784', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 7, question: '9502 − 4819 =', answer: '4683', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 8, question: '8510 − 3754 =', answer: '4756', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 9, question: '7362 − 4485 =', answer: '2877', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 10, question: '8263 − 4376 =', answer: '3887', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''}
];